hdsentinel.com 2019-02-01

# Privacy policy and information use

## Privacy Policy

### 1\. Introduction

Heartfelt Development Services Hungary Kft (H.D.S. Hungary) appreciates your visit on our websites and is grateful for your interest in our company, our products and our services. The protection of your privacy and personal data is an important matter for us. To ensure a high level of transparency and security, our privacy statement as set forth below will inform you about the nature, scope and purpose of any collection, use and processing of personal data recorded by us.

Our company respects each individual's right to personal privacy. We will collect and use information through our Web site and products only in the ways disclosed in this statement. This statement applies solely to information collected at [www.hdsentinel.com](https://www.hdsentinel.com/) , [www.harddisksentinel.com](https://www.harddisksentinel.com/) and [www.hdsentinel.hu](http://www.hdsentinel.hu/) Web sites, and through software available from these sites.

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of H.D.S. Hungary, concerning the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information. H.D.S. Hungary receives such information through the pages of our web site, services and software. When using any of our Services, you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. External Links

Our websites also reference and include links to third-party websites. As a rule, these are identified by stating the respective third-party Internet address or the company/product logo. H.D.S. Hungary has no influence whatsoever on the contents and design of websites of other providers. By referencing/linking these external websites we do not adopt their contents as our own.

We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information. Some third-party companies may choose to share their personal data with H.D.S. Hungary; that sharing is governed by that third-party company's privacy policy. 

### 3\. Cookie Policy

Information about our usage of cookies, especially for marketing purposes, can be found in our Cookie Policy.

### 4\. Information Collection and Use

Personal information is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. H.D.S. Hungary uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship. We take seriously the trust you place in us. H.D.S. Hungary will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect, store and manage the following types of information:

  * Names and email addresses that our users divulge when subscribing to our online services: newsletter and discussion board.

  * Cookies: A cookie is a small text file that our Web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Most browsers automatically accept cookies but generally provide a mechanism to stop accepting them or to prompt you before accepting one that is being sent. We do not require cookies for many parts of our Services but some features may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

  * Voluntary hardware information reports submitted by users. The submitted information does not contain any personal data or information stored on the computer running any products downloaded from this site. Hardware reports used only in order to improve software and services and never disclosed to 3rd parties.

  * Non-personal information: IP address, browser type and language, pages / URLs visited, search terms, referring domain, and the date and time of your request used for "geographic" statistical purposes only to improve usability of our web sites.

### 5\. Information Use

The information collected by H.D.S. Hungary will be used solely by our company to improve our products and services and in conjunction with the specified terms in this document. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction or order, to communicate with you, to provide service and support, to update you on services and benefits, to personalize promotional offers. 

Occasionally we may to contact in e-mail for market research regarding our products or services which includes information about possible new products, software versions, services and discounts / promotional offers related to our products. 

Financial information (account number, credit card information or similar) is used only for payment processing by our financial partners processing order transactions.

Registered Sellers may receive additional announcements from us about products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our customers we present the option to not receive these types of communications.

Our Web site offers forum and message boards. For these purposes we require certain personal information from you (user name and email address), to identify users. Please keep in mind that the texts published by you may potentially be viewed by everyone on the Internet without limitation.

### 6\. Information Sharing

H.D.S. Hungary will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. H.D.S. Hungary will not share your personal information with third parties except in responding to your requests for products or services or in processing order transactions.

H.D.S. Hungary contracts with third-party service providers and suppliers to deliver complete products, services and customer solutions described in the "Information Use" section. Suppliers and service providers are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of H.D.S. Hungary and may not use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for H.D.S. Hungary. These service providers may change or we may contract with additional service providers to better accommodate our customers. H.D.S. Hungary will not share personal information with any other third parties without your permission, unless required by law enforcement action.

### 7\. Privacy Preferences

Our e-mail communication (newsletter, product updates, discounted offers) includes the possibility to revoke your consent at any time, should you no longer desire to receive such information.

In addition, you may contact us to modify your privacy preferences or completely remove all stored information regarding such communications which processed in shortest possible time.

Upon request, our Data Protection Officer would be happy to provide you with information as to whether - and if so, which - personal data we store in relation to you. Should your personal data be incorrect, you may have this rectified immediately. Any such information or modification is free of charge.

### 8\. Information Security and Integrity

H.D.S. Hungary is committed to protecting the information you provide us and keep your personal information accurate.

We have implemented the appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We also take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we store is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

### 9\. Our Policy Towards Children

H.D.S. Hungary is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. H.D.S. Hungary does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and H.D.S. Hungary does not target its websites to children under 13. 

### 10\. Changes to this Policy

Please note that we may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will govern our use of your information and will always be available at <https://www.hdsentinel.com/privacy.php>. If we make a significant change to this policy, in our sole discretion, we will notify you via email to the address we have on record. By continuing to access or use our Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

### 11\. Contact

Please feel free to direct any questions, comments, or complaints regarding this privacy statement or the privacy practices of H.D.S. Hungary to our Data Protection Officer:

Heartfelt Development Services Hungary Kft.  
Janos Mathe CEO  
34 Dozsa str.  
8142 Urhida  
Hungary  
Email: info (at) hdsentinel (dot) com 

**Latest revision: 15 May 2018.**
